Guide to The Boys' Club of New York Records 1876-2002 MS 3000
New-York Historical Society
- Series II: Programs and Operations
  - Subseries II.5: Building Operations
    - Architectural plans, Harriman (formerly Tompkins Square) Building renovations, 1995 (Oversize Medium, Folder BCNY OS 1)
    - Correspondence and memos regarding construction of Marion McMahon Abbe Clubhouse (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2039), 2001-2004 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 3-4)
- Series III: Financial Documents
  This series includes annual financial statements, audit reports, and other financial reports of the overall organization, as well as some financial statements of the Dental Clinic.
  Note that access to these records is restricted for 35 years from the date of creation. Records that were restricted at the time this finding aid was created are identified in the box and folder list.
  - Financial Statements, 1943 October 1 - 1945 September 30 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 5)
  - Financial Statements, 1945 October 1 - 1948 September 30 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 6)
  - Financial Statements, 1948 October 1 - 1950 September 30 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 7)
  - Financial Statements, 1950 October 1 - 1952 September 30 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 8)
  - Financial Statements, 1952 October 1 - 1954 September 30 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 1)
  - Financial Statements, 1954 October 1 - 1956 September 30 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 2)
  - Financial Statements, 1956 October 1 - 1958 September 30 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 3)
  - Financial Statements, 1958 October 1 - 1960 September 30 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 4)
  - Financial Statements, 1960 October 1 - 1962 September 30 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 5)
  - Financial Statements, 1962 October 1 - 1964 September 30 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 6)
  - Financial Statements, 1964 October 1 - 1966 September 30 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 1)
  - Financial Statements, 1966 October 1 - 1968 September 30 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 2)
  - Financial Statements, 1968 October 1 - 1970 September 30 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 3)
  - Financial Statements, 1970 October 1 - 1972 September 30 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 4)
  - Financial Statements, 1972 October 1 - 1974 September 30 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 5)
  - Financial Statements, 1974 October 1 - 1976 September 30 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 1)
  - Financial Statements, 1976 October 1 - 1977 September 30 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 2)
  - Treasurer's Annual Report, 1977-1980 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 3)
  - Financial Statements, 1979 October 1 - 1980 September 30 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 4)
  - Treasurer's Annual Report, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 5)
  - Trustee Production (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2023), 1988 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 6)
  - Financial Statements (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2032), 1996-1997 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 1-11)
  - Audit Reports, 1927-1938 (Box 35 (tall box))
  - Audit Reports, 1944-1949 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 1)
  - Audit Reports, 1950-1955 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 2)
  - Audit Reports, 1956-1959 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 3)
  - Audit Reports, 1960-1964 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 4)
  - Audit Reports, 1965-1968 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 5)
  - Audit Reports, 1969-1971 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 1)
  - Audit Reports, 1972-1974 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 2)
  - Dental Clinic Ledger, 1941-1958 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 3)
  - Dental Clinic Ledger (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2035), 2000 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 4-5)
  - Dental Clinic Ledger (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2036), 2001 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 1-2)
  - Dental Clinic Monthly Financial Statements (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2037), 2002 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 3-4)
  - Bills and correspondence (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2036), 1990's - 2001 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 5)
  - Endowment ledger, 1970's - ? (Offsite-box 35, Folder unknown container)
  - Endowment funds, 1950's - 1970's (Offsite-box 39, Folder 1)
  - Investments and bequests, 1920's (Offsite-box 39, Folder 2)
  - Investment report (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2038), 2002-2003 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 3-4)
- Series IV: Publications and Articles
  - Subseries IV.1: Annual Reports
    Spanning the period from 1890 to 2003, the Annual Reports provide an excellent overview of BCNY's activities and philosophy and the organization's evolution over time. They are also a rich source of information about the neighborhoods in which BCNY operated (the East Village, the Lower East Side, and Harlem), and about the economic and social conditions of the times. For example, the 1917 Annual Report includes a photograph of a minstrel show performed by the boys; the 1925 Annual Report is titled "A Flame Beneath the Melting Pot;" and the 1941-1942 Annual Report focuses on "Training for Service" and "Men of the Post-War World." Beginning in 1907, reports are illustrated with photographs depicting clubhouse and camp activities and, occasionally, neighborhood scenes. Annual reports also reflect the evolution of social work in America.
    - Annual Reports, 1890, 1891, 1895, 1896 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 5)
    - Annual Report, 1897 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 6)
    - Annual Report, 1900 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 7)
    - Annual Report, 1901 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 8)
    - Annual Report, 1903 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 9)
    - Annual Report, 1904 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 10)
    - Annual Report, 1906 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 11)
    - Annual Report, 1907 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 1)
    - Annual Report, 1908 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 2)
    - Annual Report, 1909 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 3)
    - Annual Report, 1910 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 4)
    - Annual Report, 1911 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 5)
    - Annual Report, 1912 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 6)
    - Annual Report, 1913 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 7)
    - Annual Report, 1914 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 8)
    - Annual Report, 1916 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 9)
    - Annual Report, 1917 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 10)
    - Annual Report, 1918 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 11)
    - Annual Report, 1919-1920 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 12)
    - Annual Report, 1920-1921 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 13)
    - Annual Report, 1923-1924 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 14)
    - Annual Report, 1924-1925 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 15)
    - Annual Reports, 1925-1927 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 1)
    - Annual Reports/Boys' Club Quarterly, 1927-1928 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 2)
    - Annual Reports/Boys' Club Quarterly, 1929-1930 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 3)
    - Annual Reports/Boys' Club Quarterly, 1931-1933 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 4)
    - Annual Reports/Boys' Club Quarterly, 1934-1936 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 5)
    - Annual Reports, 1937-1938 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 6)
    - Annual Reports, 1939-1940, 1946-1947 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 7)
    - Annual Reports, 1948-1949 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 8)
    - Annual Reports, 1950-1951 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 9)
    - Annual Reports, 1952-1953 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 10)
    - Annual Reports, 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 11)
    - Annual Reports, 1956-1958 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 12)
    - Annual Reports, 1956-1958 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 12)
    - Annual Reports, 1959-1961 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 13)
    - Annual Reports, 1962-1964 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 14)
    - Annual Reports (Offsite-box 41, Folder 15)
    - Annual Reports, 1968-1970 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 16)
    - Annual Reports, 1971-1973 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 17)
    - Annual Reports, 1974-1976 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 18)
    - Annual Reports, 1977-1979 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 19)
    - Annual Reports, 1980-1982 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 20)
    - Annual Reports, 1983-1985 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 21)
    - Annual Reports, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 22)
    - Annual Reports, 1989-1991 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 23)
    - Annual Reports (Offsite-box 42, Folder 1)
    - Annual Reports, 1996-1997 (Offsite-box 42, Folder 2)
    - Annual Reports, 1998-2000 (Offsite-box 42, Folder 3)
    - Annual Reports, 2001-2003 (Offsite-box 42, Folder 4)
    - Reports of The Boys' Club (bound volume), 1891-1923 (Offsite-box 42, Folder 5)
    - Reports of The Boys' Club (bound volume), 1924-1943 (Offsite-box 42, Folder 6)
    - Annual Report worksheets, 1943-1056 (Offsite-box 43, Folder 1-2)
    - Annual reports correspondence and receipts, 1990's (Offsite-box 43, Folder 3)
    - Annual Report mockups, undated (Offsite-box 43, Folder 4)
  - Subseries IV.2: Pamphlets and Newsletters
    This subseries consists of pamphlets and newsletters issued by BCNY, the former to solicit funds and volunteers, and the latter to highlight current programs and the achievements of individual members and staff. Pamphlets include images and many summarize BCNY's achievements, providing capsule histories of the organization. Like the Annual Reports, they are also a good source of information about economic and social trends.
    - Promotional pamphlets, circa 1940's-2000's (Offsite-box 43, Folder 5-7)
    - Promotional pamphlets (oversize) (Offsite-box 43A, Folder 1)
    - Pamphlets - buildings and programs, circa 1940's - 1990's (Offsite-box 44, Folder 1)
    - "News Briefs"; "What's Happening at BCNY"; "Club Notes", 1970, undated (Offsite-box 44, Folder 2)
    - "Mentor," A quarterly publication of the BCNY Education Alumni Association, 1990's (Offsite-box 44, Folder 3)
  - Subseries IV.3: Boys' Publications
    This subseries consists primarily of issues of The Boys' Club Record, an in-house publication of the boys containing news of Club activities and events, as well as reports of individual members' achievements. Published between the 1890's and 1960's, the Record provides information about the small "clubs" into which the boys were organized (for example, the Senior Club, the Law & Order Club, the Dramatic and Debating Club, etc.), and about athletic events, lectures, dances, theatrical productions, and other clubhouse activities. Some issues also contain essays and profiles of members.
    The Record was published monthly. The collection includes both loose copies and issues that were bound together by BCNY for their library.
    In addition to the Record, this subseries includes various other publications by individual clubs within BCNY.
    - Bound Volumes
      - The Boys' Club Record:1904-1916 (Offsite-box 148, Volume 1)
      - The Boys' Club Record: 1916-1922 (Offsite-box 148, Volume 2)
      - The Boys' Club Record: 1924-1926 (Offsite-box 149, Volume 3)
      - The Boys' Club Record: 1928-1929 (Offsite-box 149, Volume 4)
      - The Boys' Club Record: 1929-1930 (Offsite-box 149, Volume 5)
      - The Boys' Club Record: 1930-1931 (Offsite-box 149, Volume 6)
      - The Boys' Club Record: 1931-1932 (Offsite-box 149, Volume 7)
      - The Boys' Club Record: 1932-1933 (Offsite-box 148, Volume 8)
      - The Boys' Club Record: 1933-1934 (Offsite-box 148, Volume 9)
      - The Boys' Club Record: 1934-1935 (Offsite-box 148, Volume 10)
      - The Boys' Club Record: 1935-1936 (Offsite-box 148, Volume 11)
      - The Boys' Club Record: 1936-1937 (Offsite-box 148, Volume 12)
      - The Boys' Club Record: 1937-1938 (Offsite-box 148, Volume 13)
      - The Boys' Club Record: 1939-1940 (Offsite-box 148, Volume 14)
      - The Boys' Club Record: 1940-1941 (Offsite-box 150, Volume 15)
      - The Boys' Club Record: 1941-1942 (Offsite-box 150, Volume 16)
      - The Boys' Club Records: 1942-1943 (Offsite-box 150, Volume 17)
      - The Boys' Club Record: 1943-1944 (Offsite-box 150, Volume 18)
      - The Boys' Club Record: 1944-1945 (Offsite-box 150, Volume 19)
      - The Boys' Club Record: 1945-1946 (Offsite-box 150, Volume 20)
      - The Boys' Club Record: 1947 (Offsite-box 115, Volume 21)
      - The Boys' Club Record:1947-1948 (Offsite-box 150, Volume 22)
      - The Boys' Club Records: 1948-1949 (Offsite-box 150, Volume 23)
      - The Boys' Club Records: 1949-1950 (Offsite-box 150, Volume 24)
      - The Boys' Club Record: 1950-1951 (Offsite-box 150, Volume 25)
      - The Boys' Club Record: 1951-1952 (Offsite-box 150, Volume 26)
      - The Boys' Club Record: 1952-1953 (Offsite-box 150, Volume 27)
      - The Boys' Club Records: 1953-1954 (Offsite-box 150, Volume 28)
      - The Boys' Club Record: 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 151, Volume 29)
      - The Boys' Club Record: 1955-1956 (Offsite-box 151, Volume 30)
      - The Boys' Club Record: 1956-1957 (Offsite-box 151, Volume 31)
      - The Junior World: 1940-1941 (Offsite-box 151, Volume 32)
      - Literary Corner of The Boys' Club Library: Volume 1. 1933-1934, Volume 2. 1934-1935, 1933-1935 (Offsite-box 151, Volume 33)
      - Literary Corner of The Boys' Club Library: Volume 3. 1935-1936, Volume 4. 1936-1937, 1935-1937 (Offsite-box 151, Volume 34)
      - Literary Corner of The Boys' Club Library: Volume 5. 1937-1938, Volume 6. 1938-1939, 1937-1939 (Offsite-box 151, Volume 35)
      - Literary Corner of The Boys' Club Library: Volume 7. 1939-1940, Volume 8. 1940-1941, 1939-1941 (Offsite-box 151, Volume 36)
    - Loose copies
      - Boys' Club Record, 1899-1905 (Offsite-box 44, Folder 4)
      - Boys' Club Record, 1916-1917 (Offsite-box 44, Folder 6)
      - Boys' Club Record, 1918 (Offsite-box 44, Folder 7)
      - Boys' Club Record, 1919-1920 (Offsite-box 44, Folder 8)
      - Boys' Club Record, Golden Jubilee Number, 1927 (Offsite-box 44, Folder 9)
      - Boys' Club Record, 1927-1930 (Offsite-box 43A, Folder 2-5)
      - Boys' Club Record, 1937-1938, undated (Offsite-box 44, Folder 10)
      - Boys' Club Record, 1945-1946 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 2)
      - Boys' Club Record, 1947, 1957-1958 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 3)
      - Boys' Club Record, 1957-1959 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 4)
      - Boys' Club Record, 1958-1959 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 5)
      - Boys' Club Record; Pitt Street Boys' Club Record, 1959-1960 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 6)
      - Boys' Club Record, 1961-1962 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 7)
      - Boys' Club Highlights, 1969 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 7)
      - Cardinal Athletic Club, 1935-1937, 1939, 1941 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 1)
      - Millrose Athletic Club "News", 1933-1934 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 2)
      - Millrose Athletic Club "News", 1934-1935 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 3)
      - Redfoot Athletic Club "Arrow", 1934 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 4)
      - Corner-Side's Spider, undated (Offsite-box 46, Folder 5)
      - Premier's Athletic Club Yearbook, 1937-1938 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 6)
      - Premier's Athletic Club Yearbook, 1940 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 7)
      - Senior Club "Review," "Mouthpiece" and Fifth Annual Benefit Dance, 1939, undated (Offsite-box 46, Folder 8)
      - Senior Club "Flash", 1935-1937, 1940, undated (Offsite-box 46, Folder 9)
      - "Spades" Yearbook, 1941-1942 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 1)
      - "Jaguar Broadcaster" (includes correspondence and photograph of group leader Edward Leadbeater), 1936-1938 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 2)
      - "Jaguar" Yearbook, 1938-1946 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 3)
      - "Junior World"; "Arcade Traveler"; "White Sox Gazette", 1930's - 1940's (Offsite-box 47, Folder 4)
      - Pitt Tigers Report; BCNY Magazine, 1984, 2011 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 5)
  - Subseries IV.4: Articles
    This subseries contains newspaper clippings and magazine articles about BCNY and people associated with the organization. Magazines featuring BCNY advertisements are also included.
    - News clippings, 1928-1930 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 6)
    - News clippings, 1930's - 2000's (Offsite-box 47, Folder 7)
    - News clippings -- obituaries, 1960's - 1990's (Offsite-box 47, Folder 8)
    - Magazine articles and advertisements, 1885 - 1950's (Offsite-box 48, Folder 1-2)
    - Magazine articles and advertisements, 2000's (Offsite-box 48, Folder 3)
    - Magazine articles and advertisements -- "People" feature, 1985 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 4)
    - Magazine articles and advertisements -- Guaranty Trust Co. "The Guaranty News", 1956, 1957 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 5)
    - Magazine articles and advertisements -- Brown Brothers Harriman "Communicator", 1978, 1981 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 6)
    - Magazine articles (oversize) -- Fortune magazine, 1932 (Offsite-box 43A, Folder 6)
    - Newspaper articles, London boxing match (oversize), 1953 (Offsite-box 43A, Folder 7)
    - Articles and advertisements (oversize), 1950's - 2000's (Offsite-box 43A, Folder 8)
    - "The Boys' Club and Juvenile Delinquency", 1936, 1984 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 7)
  - Subseries IV.5: Histories
    This subseries includes a history of BCNY, written by Sharon Zane for the organization in 1990, as well as various other historical sketches, reminiscences, and interview transcripts. There is also some correspondence relating to these projects.
    - Boys' Club of New York: A History by Sharon Zane, 1990 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 8-9)
    - Correspondence with Sharon Zane, 1986-1989 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 1)
    - Articles and pamphlets, 1922, 1960's, undated (Offsite-box 49, Folder 2)
    - Historical sketches and recollections, 1920's - 1930's, undated (Offsite-box 49, Folder 3)
    - Historical sketches and recollections, 1960's - 1980's, undated (Offsite-box 49, Folder 4)
    - Minot K. Milliken, Oral history and remarks, 1985 (Offsite-box 49, Folder unknown container)
    - Transcript, interview with Brad Zervas, 2005 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence regarding historical materials, 1950's - 1990's (Offsite-box 49, Folder 7)
  - Subseries IV.6: Other Publications
    This subseries includes a book of quotations for public speakers, and a published book about E.H. Harriman and his estate, Arden Farms.
    - "The Public Speaker's Treasure Chest", 1942 (Offsite-box 151, Volume 37)
    - "E.H. Harriman at Arden Farms", 1997 (Offsite-box 151, Volume 38)
- Series V: Alumni Association
  The Alumni Association was formed in 1928 to "assist the Boys' Club Trustees in the successful management of the Club." Open to all former BCNY members, the Alumni Association contributed both funds and volunteer services to current BCNY members. Papers include meeting minutes, correspondence, newsletters, event programs, and other material relating to the activities of the Alumni Association.
  Also included are the reminiscences and scrapbooks of George Flatow, an early Club member and one of the founding members of the Alumni Association. Flatow wrote detailed descriptions of and anecdotes from BCNY's early days, and also profiled club members from that era, describing their contributions to the club as well as their subsequent careers. Notable examples include soccer star Nathan Agar; Aaron Chwatt, better known as comedian and actor "Red Buttons;" racecar champion Ralph DePalma; and vaudeville comedian Edward Hastings Ford. While they are personal recollections, rather than a reliable factual record, Flatow's writings offer a unique perspective on the Club's early history and on the experience of urban life in early twentieth century New York City.
  - Alumni Association formation, 1928 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Association Minutes, 1944-1951 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 2)
  - Alumni Association Minutes, 1952-1955 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Association Minutes, 1956-1959 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Association Minutes, 1960-1965 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Association Minutes, 1960-1963 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Association Minutes, 1964-1971 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Association Minutes, 1971-1975 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Association Minutes, 1979-1984 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 2)
  - Alumni "Bulletin", 1945-1947, 1949 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Newsletter, 1950's (Offsite-box 51, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Newsletter, 1965-1970 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Newsletter, 1980's - 1990's, 2010 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 6)
  - Alumni lists and history, 1990's, undated (Offsite-box 51, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Association correspondence, 1981-1995, 2000-2001 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 8)
  - Alumni Association correspondence (Pitt Street/Milliken Building), 1984-1990 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 9)
  - Alumni Association correspondence (Jefferson Park Building), 1985-1996 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, "Friends for Life" video; Florida Alumni Association; National Alumni Association, 1983-2003 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, George Flatow, 1928-1981 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, George Flatow, 1981-1986 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence/Addresses, George Flatow (Offsite-box 52, Folder 4)
  - Addresses/Recollections, George Flatow, undated (Offsite-box 52, Folder 5)
  - Anecdotes, George Flatow, 1974 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 6)
  - Recollections "A-E", George Flatow, 1974 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 7)
  - Recollections "F-J", George Flatow, 1974 (Offsite-box 53, Folder 1)
  - Recollections "K-Z", George Flatow, 1974 (Offsite-box 53, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook, George Flatow, 1980's (Offsite-box 53, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook, George Flatow (Offsite-box 123 (flat box), Folder 1-2)
  - Scrapbook, George Flatow, 1920's - 1960's (Offsite-box 127, Folder 1-5)
  - Alumni Annual Ball Programs, 1950's - 1960's (Offsite-box 53, Folder 4-6)
  - Programs, Alumni Anniversary Celebrations, 1980's - 1990's (Offsite-box 53, Folder 7)
  - Souvenir Program, "Damn Yankees", 1999 (Offsite-box 53, Folder 8)
- Series VI: Benefit Events and Fundraising
  This series contains correspondence and ephemera (invitations, programs, raffle tickets, etc.) from various benefit events sponsored by the Women's Board, including the Fall and Spring Dances, theater and movie benefits, fashion shows, golf benefits, and assorted others. Invitations are often elaborate and provide interesting examples of graphic design work. For photographs of these events, see Series VII.
  Also included are disbound binders of photographs, invitations, seating charts and other material relating to BCNY's largest annual benefit, the All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner. This event honored Hall of Fame inductees from six major sports (football, baseball, basketball, hockey, tennis and golf).
  Other materials relating to fundraising include sample materials from BCNY's annual Christmas drive and correspondence files. Note that correspondence files are restricted for 35 years from the date of creation. Files that were restricted at the time this finding aid was created are identified in the box and folder list.
  - Subseries VI.1: Benefit Events
    - Fall Dance, correspondence, 1955 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 1)
    - Fall Dance, correspondence, 1956 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 2)
    - Fall Dance, correspondence, 1957 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 3)
    - Fall Dance, correspondence, 1958 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 4)
    - Fall Dance, correspondence, 1959 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 5)
    - Fall Dance, correspondence, 1960 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 6)
    - Fall Dance, correspondence, 1961 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 1)
    - Fall Dance, correspondence, 1962 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 2)
    - Fall Dance, correspondence, 1963 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 3)
    - Fall Dance, correspondence, 1964 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 4)
    - Fall Dance, correspondence (Offsite-box 55, Folder 5)
    - Fall Dance, correspondence, 1981 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 1)
    - Fall Dance, correspondence, 1985 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 2-3)
    - Fall Dance, correspondence, 1986 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 4)
    - Fall Dance, correspondence, 1987 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 5)
    - Fall Dance, correspondence, 1990 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 6)
    - Fall Dance, invitations, 1955 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 1)
    - Fall Dance, invitations, 1956 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 2)
    - Fall Dance, invitations, 1957 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 3)
    - Fall Dance, invitations, 1958-1959 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 4)
    - Fall Dance, invitations, 1960-1961 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 5)
    - Fall Dance, invitations, 1962 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 6)
    - Fall Dance, invitations, 1963-1964 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 7)
    - Fall Dance, invitations, 1965-1966 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 8)
    - Fall Dance, invitations, 1967-1968 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 9)
    - Fall Dance, invitations, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 1)